(Howard:)Where are the guys?
(Bernadette:)Oh, it's just me.
(Howard:)Oh, I get it. They're waiting, back home,
with a big surprise party.
(Howard:)Don't worry.
I can act surprised.
(Bernadette:)No, I told them
they could have you tomorrow night.
(Bernadette:)Tonight, you belong to me.
- Gesundheit. You okay?
- I am now that you're back.
(Bernadette:)Come on, let's go home,
so I can tear off those little pants.
(Howard:)Great. Just keep in mind astronauts lose
a lot of muscle tone in space...
(Howard:)...so you might have to do
most of the heavy lifting.
(Sheldon:)Now, I am very disappointed
that I won't be able to celebrate...
(Sheldon:)...Howard's accomplishment tonight.
- Me too, but we'll see him tomorrow.
(Sheldon:)Yes, it's just that
in all the years I've known him...
(Sheldon:)...he's never had the opportunity
to receive my admiration.
(Sheldon:)I was excited to see the look
on his face when it finally happened.
(Penny:)You're unbelievable.